{"data":{"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"2151","name":"White Castle #43","address":"15365 Wyoming Ave","zipcode":"48238","owner":"White Castle System, Inc.","licenseNumber":"040563","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":null,"reviewFrequencyDays":"365.0","coords":"-83.16005,42.40361","geojson":{"id":"2151","type":"Feature","geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[-83.160047385,42.4036069270001]},"properties":{"name":"White Castle #43","owner":"White Castle System, Inc.","address":"15365 Wyoming Ave","zipcode":"48238","license_type":"Fixed Establishment","risk_category":null,"license_number":"040563","establishmentid":"2151","establishment_type":"Food Service Establishment","establishment_status":"Open","review_frequency_days":"365.0","most_recent_license_date":"5/4/2018"}},"nearbyList":[{"establishmentid":"1282","name":"Tim Horton's","address":"15340 Wyoming Ave","zipcode":"48238"},{"establishmentid":"1289","name":"McDonald's #3146","address":"15321 Wyoming Ave","zipcode":"48238"},{"establishmentid":"51622637","name":"Jam Jomar XXV III (McDonalds)","address":"15321 Wyoming #3146","zipcode":"48238"},{"establishmentid":"51622478","name":"Pizza Kebab","address":"15221 Wyoming Ave","zipcode":"48238"},{"establishmentid":"4067","name":"China Garden","address":"15228 Wyoming Ave","zipcode":"48238"},{"establishmentid":"4913","name":"Wyoming Fresh Fish","address":"15151 Wyoming Ave","zipcode":"48238"},{"establishmentid":"4914","name":"Loyola High School Detroit","address":"15325 Pinehurst","zipcode":"48238"},{"establishmentid":"4665","name":"Faustina's Creole and Soulfood","address":"16155 Wyoming Ave","zipcode":"48221"},{"establishmentid":"1868","name":"WE Care Senior Meal Program","address":"8720 Puritan ","zipcode":"48238"},{"establishmentid":"2744","name":"Super 3 Coney Island","address":"14508 Wyoming Ave","zipcode":"48238"}],"inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"42622","inspectionDate":"2018-06-21T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"With accumulation of debris","subProblem":"","location":"THROUGHOUT FACILITY","subLocation":"NON FOOD CONTACT SURFACES","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."},{"violationCode":"5-205.15","violationDescription":"A PLUMBING SYSTEM shall be:\r\n(A) Repaired according to LAW; (P) and\r\n(B) Maintained in good repair.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Plumbing system","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"MOP SINK AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Maintain in good repair"},{"violationCode":"4-602.11","violationDescription":"(A) Equipment FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be cleaned:     \r\n  (1) Except as specified in ¶ (B) of this section, before each use with a different   type of raw animal FOOD such as beef, FISH, lamb, pork, or POULTRY; (P)   \r\n  (2) Each time there is a change from working with raw FOODS to working with   READY-TO-EAT FOODS; (P)   \r\n  (3) Between uses with raw fruits and vegetables and with POTENTIALLY   HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD);   (P)   \r\n  (4) Before using or storing a FOOD TEMPERATURE MEASURING   DEVICE; (P) and   \r\n  (5) At any time during the operation when contamination may have occurred. (P)\r\n(B) Subparagraph (A)(1) of this section does not apply if the FOOD-CONTACT SURFACE or UTENSIL is in contact with a succession of different raw animal FOODS each requiring a higher cooking temperature as specified under § 3-401.11 than the previous FOOD, such as preparing raw FISH followed by cutting raw poultry on the same cutting board.   \r\n(C) Except as specified in ¶ (D) of this section, if used with POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD), EQUIPMENT FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be cleaned throughout the day at least every 4 hours. (P)   \r\n(D) Except when dry cleaning methods are used as specified under § 4-603.11, surfaces of UTENSILS and EQUIPMENT contacting FOOD that is not POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be cleaned:     \r\n  (1)   At any time when contamination may have occurred;\r\n  (2)   At least every 24 hours for iced tea dispensers and CONSUMER self-service UTENSILS such as tongs, scoops, or ladles;\r\n  (3) Before restocking CONSUMER self-service EQUIPMENT and UTENSILS such as condiment dispensers and display containers; and\r\n  (4) In EQUIPMENT such as ice bins and BEVERAGE dispensing nozzles and   enclosed components of EQUIPMENT such as ice makers, cooking oil storage   tanks and distribution lines, BEVERAGE and syrup dispensing lines or tubes,   coffee bean grinders, and water vending EQUIPMENT:\r\n     (a) At a frequency specified by the manufacturer, or\r\n     (b) Absent manufacturer specifications, at a frequency necessary to preclude      accumulation of soil or mold.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Food-contact surface(s) used for nonpotentially hazardous food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not cleaned","subProblem":"","location":"PREP AREA(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean as required above."},{"violationCode":"6-501.18","violationDescription":"PLUMBING FIXTURES such as HANDWASHING SINKS, toilets, and urinals shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean. \r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"sink","subItem":"handwash","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"Throughout","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean"},{"violationCode":"6-501.16","violationDescription":"After use, mops shall be placed in a position that allows them to air-dry without soiling walls, EQUIPMENT, or supplies.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Wet mop(s) storage","subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"STORAGE AREA (DRY)","subLocation":"Mop","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"6-501.18","violationDescription":"PLUMBING FIXTURES such as HANDWASHING SINKS, toilets, and urinals shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean. \r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Handwashing facility","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"RESTROOM (WOMEN'S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean."},{"violationCode":"4-501.14","violationDescription":"A WAREWASHING machine; the compartments of sinks, basins, or  other receptacles used for washing and rinsing EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, or raw FOODS, or laundering wiping cloths; and drainboards or other EQUIPMENT used to substitute for drainboards shall be cleaned as required.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Warewashing equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not cleaned","subProblem":"","location":"3 COMPARTMENT SINK AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean as required above."},{"violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\r\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"","problemDescription":"With accumulation of debris","subProblem":"","location":"THROUGHOUT FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."}]},{"inspectionid":"42329","inspectionDate":"2018-05-11T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Complaint","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"39150","inspectionDate":"2017-07-03T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-101.11","violationDescription":"FOOD shall be safe, unADULTERATED and honestly presented. (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Food","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Dishonestly presented","subProblem":"","location":"STORAGE AREA (DRY)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-07-03T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Discard"},{"violationCode":"4-602.11","violationDescription":"(A) Equipment FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be cleaned:     \r\n  (1) Except as specified in ¶ (B) of this section, before each use with a different   type of raw animal FOOD such as beef, FISH, lamb, pork, or POULTRY; (P)   \r\n  (2) Each time there is a change from working with raw FOODS to working with   READY-TO-EAT FOODS; (P)   \r\n  (3) Between uses with raw fruits and vegetables and with POTENTIALLY   HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD);   (P)   \r\n  (4) Before using or storing a FOOD TEMPERATURE MEASURING   DEVICE; (P) and   \r\n  (5) At any time during the operation when contamination may have occurred. (P)\r\n(B) Subparagraph (A)(1) of this section does not apply if the FOOD-CONTACT SURFACE or UTENSIL is in contact with a succession of different raw animal FOODS each requiring a higher cooking temperature as specified under § 3-401.11 than the previous FOOD, such as preparing raw FISH followed by cutting raw poultry on the same cutting board.   \r\n(C) Except as specified in ¶ (D) of this section, if used with POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD), EQUIPMENT FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be cleaned throughout the day at least every 4 hours. (P)   \r\n(D) Except when dry cleaning methods are used as specified under § 4-603.11, surfaces of UTENSILS and EQUIPMENT contacting FOOD that is not POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be cleaned:     \r\n  (1)   At any time when contamination may have occurred;\r\n  (2)   At least every 24 hours for iced tea dispensers and CONSUMER self-service UTENSILS such as tongs, scoops, or ladles;\r\n  (3) Before restocking CONSUMER self-service EQUIPMENT and UTENSILS such as condiment dispensers and display containers; and\r\n  (4) In EQUIPMENT such as ice bins and BEVERAGE dispensing nozzles and   enclosed components of EQUIPMENT such as ice makers, cooking oil storage   tanks and distribution lines, BEVERAGE and syrup dispensing lines or tubes,   coffee bean grinders, and water vending EQUIPMENT:\r\n     (a) At a frequency specified by the manufacturer, or\r\n     (b) Absent manufacturer specifications, at a frequency necessary to preclude      accumulation of soil or mold.","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Food-contact surface(s) used for nonpotentially hazardous food(s)","subItem":"ice bin(s) in ice machine","problemDescription":"Not cleaned when contaminated","subProblem":"","location":"ICE MACHINE","subLocation":"","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean properly when contaminated."},{"violationCode":"3-501.17","violationDescription":"(A)  READY-TO-EAT, POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  prepared and held refrigerated for more than 24 hours in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT  shall be clearly marked at the time of preparation to indicate the date or day by which the FOOD shall be consumed. (Pf)\r\n(B)  A container of refrigerated, commercially prepared READY-TO-EAT POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  shall be clearly marked, at the time the original container is opened in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT, to indicate the date or day by which the FOOD shall be consumed. (Pf)\r\n\r\nA date marking system that does not exceed 7 days, including date of preparation, or opening is to be used. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Commercially processed ready to eat potentially hazardous food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Without date of consumption marking","subProblem":"","location":"COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Datemark with a discard date of 7 days or less."}]}]}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"2151"}}